Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  - Governor of Pennsylvania, 1979-1987; 9.
    - Events and People
      - George S. Snyder Establishment 100th Anniversary (Rep. Robert Godshall), Montgomery County, PA (2), February 11, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 27)
      - Sosnowski, Margaret Jean, Deputy Secretary for Department of Public Welfare (1), undated (Box 1517, Folder 28)
      - Soviet Jewry Council of the Jewish Community Relations Council (1), September 7, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 29)
      - Soviet Jewry Meeting (8), November 23, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 30)
      - Special Olympics, West Chester, PA (2), 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 31)
      - Sports(9), 1979-1986 (Box 1517, Folder 32)
      - Sports and Outdoor Show, Farm Show Building (9), February 8, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 33)
      - Sports and Outdoor Show, Farm Show Building (5), February 10, 1982 (Box 1517, Folder 34)
      - Sports and Outdoor Show, Farm Show Building (7), undated (Box 1517, Folder 35)
      - Sportsmen (4), undated (Box 1517, Folder 36)
      - Staff (4), 1979-1986 (Box 1517, Folder 37)
      - State Correctional Institute at Dallas, Ribbon Cutting Ceremony for New Cell Blocks (5), September 4, 1985 (Box 1517, Folder 38)
      - State Correctional Institute at Schuylkill County (3), August 13, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 39)
      - Stevens, President Siaka of Sierra Leone (2), October 30, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 40)
      - Stewart, Jimmy, Harrisburg, PA (5), May 1, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 41)
      - Stewart, Jimmy, Indiana, PA (2), May 20, 1983 (Box 1517, Folder 42)
      - Sullivan, Reverend Leon, Philadelphia, PA (4), October 1, 1980 (Box 1517, Folder 43)
      - Superior Court/Commonwealth Court Reception and Dinner (25), May 9, 1983 (Box 1517, Folder 44)
      - Supreme Court Dinner at Governor's Home (20), May 18, 1981 (Box 1517, Folder 45)
      - Tall Ship Ceremony with Mayor Bill Green and Walter Cronkite, Philadelphia, PA (7), June 17, 1982 (Box 1517, Folder 46)
      - Teacher of the Year Award Presentation, Harrisburg (1), November 16, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 47)
      - Temple University Commencement, Philadelphia, PA (7), May 24, 1979 (Box 1517, Folder 48)
      - Temple University Hospital Groundbreaking Ceremony with Mayor Bill Green (4), March 8, 1983 (Box 1517, Folder 49)
      - Temple University School of Law with Carl E. Singley, Dean (1), September 19, 1984 (Box 1517, Folder 50)
      - Thanksgiving Turkey Presented by the PA Poultry Federation (1), November 16, 1981 (Box 1517, Folder 51)
      - Thornburgh, Governor Dick, Fiftieth Birthday (4), July 16, 1982 (Box 1518, Folder 1)
      - Three Mile Island (9), March-April, 1979 (Box 1518, Folder 2)
      - Three Mile Island Clean-Up (13), 1980 (Box 1518, Folder 3)
      - Three Mile Island Tenth Anniversary Dinner, Washington, DC (1), March 22, 1989 (Box 1518, Folder 4)
      - Three Springs Senior Center Check Presentation, Three Springs, PA (2), April 25, 1985 (Box 1518, Folder 5)
      - Tolson, Jay and Congressman James Coyne (1), August, 1981 (Box 1518, Folder 6)
      - Town Meeting, Lancaster, PA (26), December, 18, 1979 (Box 1518, Folder 7)
      - Trello, Rep. Fred (3), 1980 (Box 1518, Folder 8)
      - Tullio, Mayor Louis, Erie, PA (7), undated (Box 1518, Folder 9)
      - U.S.S. Pittsburgh Commissioning (6), November 23, 1985 (Box 1518, Folder 10)
      - University of Pennsylvania Clinical Tower Groundbreaking Ceremony, Philadelphia, PA (3), September 21, 1984 (Box 1518, Folder 11)
      - University of Pittsburgh Applied Research Center (2), March 17, 1986 (Box 1518, Folder 12)
      - University of Pittsburgh Commencement (16), April 29, 1984 (Box 1518, Folder 13)
      - Updike, John (1), May 3, 1983 (Box 1518, Folder 14)
      - Ursinus College Commencement, Honorary LLD (2), May 18, 1986 (Box 1518, Folder 15)
      - U.S.S. Steel Homestead Works, 1980 (Box 1518, Folder 16-17)
      - Vermeil, Dick, Coach of Philadelphia Eagles, Mike Bortnicker, President of Delaware Chamber of Commerce, and John Boyer of Philadelphia Sub Water Company (1), April 2, 1980 (Box 1518, Folder 18)
      - Veterans of Foreign War (38), 1979-1986 (Box 1518, Folder 19)
      - Veterans/American Legion Baseball World Series, Pottstown, PA (1), September 1, 1982 (Box 1518, Folder 20)
      - Veterans/American Legion, 64th Annual Convention and Memorial Service, Philadelphia (1), July 15, 1982 (Box 1518, Folder 21)
      - Veterans/American Legion Korean War Statue Dedication and Reception, Wormleysburg, PA (4), June 10, 1984 (Box 1518, Folder 22)
      - Veterans/Disabled Americans, 52nd Annual Convention, Washington, PA (3), June 24, 1982 (Box 1518, Folder 23)
      - Veterans/Erie Soldiers and Sailors Home, Ribbon cutting and Centennial Reception, November 11, 1983 and September 24, 1986 (Box 1518, Folder 24)
      - Veterans Medal of Honor Recipients Ceremony and Luncheon, Harrisburg (2), September 26, 1983 (Box 1518, Folder 25)
      - Villanova University "Wildcat" Basketball Team, 1985 Champions of NCAA (10), April 17, 1985 (Box 1518, Folder 26)
      - Vision Through Art (1), April 28, 1985 (Box 1518, Folder 27)
      - Easter Egg Hunt for the Visually Impaired, Harrisburg, PA, April, 1979 (Box 1518, Folder 28)
      - Volkswagen of America (3), March 20, 1983 (Box 1518, Folder 29)
      - Volkswagen Plant, New Stanton, PA, One Millionth Produced (3), November 14, 1985 (Box 1519, Folder 1)
      - vonWeizsacken, Richard (1), undated (Box 1519, Folder 2)
      - Vulcan Mold and Iron Company, Latrobe, PA (1), October 7, 1980 (Box 1519, Folder 3)
      - Waghorn's Caricature of Governor Dick Thornburgh from the Phoenix Gazette, May 19, 1982 (Box 1519, Folder 4)
      - Waring, Fred (1), September 27, 1980 (Box 1519, Folder 5)
      - Wass, Rep. Paul (1), November 1, 1980 (Box 1519, Folder 6)
      - Weaber, Gregory, Muscular Dystrophy Association Poster Child (1), June 1, 1981 (Box 1519, Folder 7)
      - Webber, Mary, Swearing-In Ceremony as Special Deputy Secretary for Environmental Resources, Harrisburg (2), June 27, 1980 (Box 1519, Folder 8)
      - Weinberger, Secretary Casper (1), July 6, 1982 (Box 1519, Folder 9)
      - We Love Erie Day, Governor's Cup Race (3), August 24, 1979 (Box 1519, Folder 10)
      - West Germany (9), January 10, 1984 (Box 1519, Folder 11)
      - Westinghouse Productivity Center (Wesley Posvar and Robert Kirby), Pittsburgh, PA (7), August 5, 1982 (Box 1519, Folder 12)
      - West Virginia GOP Fundraising Dinner and Reception, Charleston, WV (1), June 3, 1983 (Box 1519, Folder 13)
      - Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corporation (1), November 23, 1983 (Box 1519, Folder 14)
      - Wishersham, Richard for Judge (3), November 17, 1979 (Box 1519, Folder 15)
      - Wiggins, Jim (3), July 22, 1983 (Box 1519, Folder 16)
      - Wilburn, Secretary Robert (4), undated (Box 1519, Folder 17)
      - Wilke, Reverend Harold (1), undated (Box 1519, Folder 18)
      - Williams, Pat, Vice President and General Manager of Philadelphia 76ers at Commonwealth Prayer Breakfast (1), April 23, 1985 (Box 1519, Folder 19)
      - William Penn Statue, Harrisburg, PA (1), undated (Box 1519, Folder 20)
      - Williams, Gene, Caricature of Governor and Ginny (2), undated (Box 1519, Folder 21)
      - Wilts, Roy (1), undated (Box 1519, Folder 22)
      - Wintersteen, Bonnie, 80th Birthday Party with Louise Nevelson, Philadelphia, PA (2), June 5, 1983 (Box 1519, Folder 23)
      - "Witness" Premier, Lancaster, PA (1), February 7, 1985 (Box 1519, Folder 24)
      - Women in Law Enforcement with Commissioner Dan Dunn (4), undated (Box 1519, Folder 25)
      - Wright Elementary School, Altoona, PA (7), October 22, 1985 (Box 1519, Folder 26)
      - Wroblewski, Joseph, President of Lions Clubs International Presenting Thornburgh with "Medal of Distinction" (2), April 9, 1986 (Box 1519, Folder 27)
      - Wyeth, Andrew (8), June 3, 1986 (Box 1519, Folder 28)
      - Wynette, Tammy, Harrisburg, PA (11), January 11, 1982 (Box 1519, Folder 29)
      - Yale Alumni: Jack Davy, Kinwin Wroth, Ed Mollow, Frank Royer and John Talbot at Talbot's Residence in Portland, ME (1), August, 1983 (Box 1519, Folder 30)
      - YMCA Youth, Harrisburg, PA (2), April 18, 1986 (Box 1519, Folder 31)
      - York Area Chamber of Commerce, York, PA (1), September 26, 1979 (Box 1519, Folder 32)
      - York Management Club Picnic, York, PA (6), August 15, 1979 (Box 1519, Folder 33)
      - "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania (7), 1979-1986 (Box 1519, Folder 34)
      - Zemin, Ambassador Chai, People's Republic of China, Washington, DC (4), January 28, 1980 and May 12, 1981 (Box 1519, Folder 35)
      - Zimmerman, Attorney General Roy (1), November 4, 1980 (Box 1519, Folder 36)
    - Ginny Thornburgh
      - Virginia Judson Thornburgh, Official Portrait (1), undated (Box 1520, Folder 1)
      - "The Harmony Trust" (1), 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 2)
      - Joyce Griffin (1), 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 3)
      - Williamsport Event (2), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 4)
      - Handicapped Children Event, Lancaster, PA (3), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 5)
      - Award (Small Statue of a Child) (2), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 6)
      - Award (1), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 7)
      - Penrose Hallowell, Quilt/Crafts Display (3), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 8)
      - Public Ceremony in Governor's Reception Room (1), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 9)
      - Happy 12th Anniversary/Wes (1), Spring, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 10)
      - Governor's Home Interview with Lancaster New Era, Harrisburg, PA (12), March 8, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 11)
      - Helen O'Bannon and Others (1), April 23, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 12)
      - Don Guanella School (1), May 6, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 13)
      - WHP Birthday Celebration (3), June,1979 (Box 1520, Folder 14)
      - Synod of the Trinity Honoring Reverend Fred Rogers, Grove City College, Grove City, PA (2), June 13, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 15)
      - Balloon Launch (1), June, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 16)
      - Camp for Handicapped Children (1), June, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 17)
      - Ginny, Peter, and Charlie Thornburgh at Outdoor Event (2), June, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 18)
      - International Year of the Child Event (1), June, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 19)
      - Miss Pennsylvania, Caroline Black, Governor's Home, Harrisburg, Pa (2), June 26, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 20)
      - "Speak Up for Children" Event (2), July, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 21)
      - Pennhurst Visit (3), July 23, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 22)
      - Governor and Ginny Thornburgh Visit with David Snyder Family, Lancaster, PA (7), August 14, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 23)
      - State Correctional Facility, Camp Hill, PA (4), August 31, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 24)
      - 1979 Teacher of the Year (1), Fall, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 25)
      - Farmer's Market (2), September 11, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 26)
      - Adrian Hohenwarter, Elizabethtown, PA (1), September 19, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 27)
      - Frolic Weymouth, Lady Bird Johnson, Mr. and Mrs. Henry Fonda and Jamie Wyeth, Philadelphia, PA (3), September 15, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 28)
      - Dinner Dance in Heinz Galleries, Carnegie Institute, Pittsburgh, PA (1), September 28, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 29)
      - National Arthritis Foundation Proclamation to Kent Messner (1), October 10, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 30)
      - Candidate Bob Byrd, City Council District 8, Germantown, PA (1), October 20, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 31)
      - Distinguished Daughters Luncheon, Award for Ginny Thornburgh, Harrisburg, PA (2), October 25, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 32)
      - Mrs. Gladys Barry delivers "Melissa Statue" to Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (1), October 29, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 33)
      - Shamokin Event (2), Fall, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 34)
      - Polyclinic Medical Center Country Fair, Harrisburg, PA (5), November 1, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 35)
      - Telephone Pioneer Day "Handicapped Services Exhibit", Strawberry Square, Harrisburg, PA (2), November 2, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 36)
      - Children's Hospital, December 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 37)
      - International Year of the Child Luncheon (3), December, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 38)
      - Robert Scanlon and Smithsonian/CEMREL "Reflections: The Children in America" Exhibit (1), December 6, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 39)
      - Wreath Hanging with Mary Grace Kreger, Erie (1), December 6, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 40)
      - Ballet de Jeunes, Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (2), December 12, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 41)
      - Ginny and Peter Thornburgh with Mr. Fred Rogers, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 42)
      - Ginny and Dick Thornburgh with a child with Disabilities, 1979 (Box 1520, Folder 43)
      - Tanoma Coal Company/Pohang Iron and Steel Company of Korea, Indiana, PA (2), 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 44)
      - Penrose Hallowell and Darwin Moyer (1), January, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 45)
      - Farm Show Opening (27), January 6, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 46)
      - Mt. Pocono Event (1), January 17, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 47)
      - Pennsylvania School for the Deaf, Philadelphia, PA (1), January 21, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 48)
      - Neighborhood Day Care, Harrisburg, PA (2), February 14, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 49)
      - Northwest/Washington County Medical Center (1), February 15, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 50)
      - Bobbie Waldman (2), Winter, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 51)
      - Gorham Black and Senior Citizens and Children (4), Winter, 1980 (Box 1520, Folder 52)
      - Japan Trip (8), March, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 1)
      - Lynn Johnson, Pittsburgh Press Interview at the Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (4), March, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 2)
      - Governor's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped (1), March, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 3)
      - Polk Center, Pittsburgh, PA (1), March 21, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 4)
      - Lenten Service at Pine Street Presbyterian Church (1), March-April, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 5)
      - Pennsylvania Women Graduates of Service Academies, Carlisle Barracks of US Army War College, Carlisle, PA (1), Spring, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 6)
      - Public Ceremony, Governor's Reception Room, Harrisburg, PA (1), Spring, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 7)
      - Statewide Art Show for the Mentally Retarded (3), April, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 8)
      - Valley Special Needs Programs (1), April 3, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 9)
      - Women's Event (1), April 15, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 10)
      - Pittsburgh YWCA Annual Dinner Meeting (1), April 17, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 11)
      - Allied Services, Scranton, PA (5), April 23, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 12)
      - Avalon Group Home, Avalon, PA (2), April 27, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 13)
      - "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania" Bureau of Travel Development Van (5), May 15, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 14)
      - Harrisburg Grant Awards (4), May 19, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 15)
      - Ronald McDonald House (4), June 4, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 16)
      - Governor's Home Art Opening (4), June 8, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 17)
      - The Ellis School (1), June 11, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 18)
      - White Haven Center, White Haven, PA (7), June 17, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 19)
      - Governor's School for the Arts (10), Summer, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 20)
      - Thornburgh Bridge Dedication (6), July 24, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 21)
      - Pennhurst Center (3), September 8, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 22)
      - Special Olympics Governor's Cup Run (7), September 14, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 23)
      - Lori Heiser (1), September 18, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 24)
      - Barbara Bush (1), September 19, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 25)
      - Pennsylvania Retired Public School Employees Association (1), October 1, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 26)
      - Moss Rehabilitation Hospital (5), October 1, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 27)
      - Governor's Council on Employment of the Handicapped Award Ceremony (6), October 10, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 28)
      - UNICEF Greater Philadelphia Area Committee CSM Baking Contest (1), October 21, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 29)
      - Elwyn Institute, Philadelphia, PA (1), November 12, 1980 (Box 1521, Folder 30)
      - ALCOA/Recycling (1), 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 31)
      - Longwood Gardens with Agnes Buchanan and Marcia Keehn (1), January 22, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 32)
      - Merv Griffin Show with Willie Mays of the New York Giants (1), February 8, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 33)
      - Veterans Administration Medical Center, Lebanon, PA (1), February 13, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 34)
      - International Year of the Disabled Persons: Arnold Muller (3), February 25, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 35)
      - Volunteer Recognition (1), April 30, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 36)
      - With Mayor Bill Green, Philadelphia, PA (2), undated, and at Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, Philadelphia (3), May 13, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 37)
      - Formal Event, Philadelphia PA (1), May 13, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 38)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art (1), May 21, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 39)
      - White Hill Graduation, Camp Hill (8), June 23, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 40)
      - People's Light and Theatre Company (1), July, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 41)
      - Bucks County Handicapped Event (11), July, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 42)
      - Virginia Judson Thornburgh, Portrait Event (2), July 10, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 43)
      - Fox Chase Cancer Center, Philadelphia, PA (4), July 10, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 44)
      - Variety Club Camp (4), July 21, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 45)
      - Senior Olympics Torch Lighting Ceremony (1), July 23, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 46)
      - Bloomingdale's Opening (1), August 2, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 47)
      - Special Olympics Governor's Cup Run (3), September 27, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 48)
      - Opening Night of Opera Company of Philadelphia (1), October 31, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 49)
      - Governor's Human Resources Committee (2), November 9, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 50)
      - Montgomery County Library Event (1), November 10, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 51)
      - Bishop McDevitt High School, Harrisburg, PA (1), November 20, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 52)
      - Three Tiered Cake (1), November 30, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 53)
      - McGuire Home of Western Pennsylvania, Beaver County with Jennifer Howse (11), December, 1981 (Box 1521, Folder 54)
      - President's Committee on Mental Retardation with Richard Schweiker and Margaret Heckler (8), 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 1)
      - 1982 Farm Show (1), January 10, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 2)
      - Three Mile Island (4), January 27, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 3)
      - Junior Women's Club of Glenside (4), February 19, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 4)
      - Retarded Citizen's Association of Dauphin County, "Hollywood Squares" Takeoff (1), March 6, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 5)
      - Art Association of Harrisburg, 52nd Annual Juried Exhibition (2), March 12, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 6)
      - Jefferson Hospital (2), April 1, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 7)
      - Mercy Hospital of Johnstown (7), April 24, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 8)
      - Mrs. Santa Raia (1), April 24, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 9)
      - Trip to England (5), May 3-7, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 10)
      - National Year of Disabled Persons Worship Service (1), May 23, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 11)
      - Three Rivers Youth, Pittsburgh, PA (3), May 27, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 12)
      - Japanese Friends (1), May 28, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 13)
      - Disabled American Veterans, Douglas-Building Complex, Camp Hill, PA (3), June 11, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 14)
      - Pennhurst Center Picnic (4), Summer, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 15)
      - St. Peter's Child Development Center (2), September 24, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 16)
      - Special Olympics Governor's Cup Run (4), September 26, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 17)
      - Edinboro State College (3), October 1, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 18)
      - Savings and Trust Company of PA, 1983 Auto Show (1), October 8, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 19)
      - Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh (6), October 19, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 20)
      - C.E.C. Luncheon, Harrisburg, PA (1), October 29, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 21)
      - St. Edmond's Facility for the Handicapped (1), October 30, 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 22)
      - Farm Event (1), 1982 (Box 1522, Folder 23)
      - ABRAXAS, President Gerald Ford (2), 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 24)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center (V.R.C.) Award, Pittsburgh, PA (3), January 26, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 25)
      - River Rescue of Harrisburg, PA (3), March 29, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 26)
      - Child Guidance Center, Philadelphia, PA (10), Spring, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 27)
      - PA State Police Academy Graduation (4), April 8, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 28)
      - The Philadelphia Award (3), April 13, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 29)
      - Valley Forge Military College and Junior College (10), May 8, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 30)
      - Cabrini College Commencement (3), May 15, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 31)
      - U.S. Israel Bilateral Conference (1), June 13, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 32)
      - Jane Seiverling with Plaque of Appreciation (4), June 18, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 33)
      - Robinson Development Center (3), Summer, 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 34)
      - Horizon House (1), 1983 (Box 1522, Folder 35)
      - Lancaster YMCA (1), January 30, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 36)
      - Buckle Up Baby (1), February 5, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 37)
      - Variety Club Telethon (1), February 5, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 38)
      - Mental Retardation Awareness Month, Public Ceremony in Governor's Reception Room, Harrisburg, PA (1), March, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 39)
      - Rotary International (1), March 2, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 40)
      - YWCA After-School Program, Harrisburg, PA (1), March 9, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 41)
      - 1984 Hall of Fame Award to Shirley Bonnem (1), March 27, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 42)
      - Scranton School for the Deaf (4), June 4, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 43)
      - Episcopal Academy, Merion, PA (1), June 7, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 44)
      - Carbon-Lehigh Intermediate Unit #22 Hand Bell Choir and Teacher of the Year Luncheon at the Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (3), June 13, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 45)
      - Special Olympics (5), 1984-1986 (Box 1522, Folder 46)
      - Allegheny County Community College Handicapped Institute (1), September 11, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 47)
      - "You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania" T-Shirt Presentation (2), September 12, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 48)
      - St. Agnes Medical Center, Philadelphia, PA (3), November 5, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 49)
      - George Washington Memorial Park Dedication, Plymouth Meeting, PA (10), November 11, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 50)
      - Handicapped Challenge Foundation, Monroeville, PA (2), November 30, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 51)
      - Pennsylvania Electoral College (1), December, 1984 (Box 1522, Folder 52)
      - 1985 Farm Show (3), January 13, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 1)
      - Five Member Delegation from Luoyang, Hunan Province in Harrisburg, PA (6), March 19, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 2)
      - Reading School District with Kay Wright (2), May 6, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 3)
      - Central PA Easter Seal Society, Bloomsburg, PA (1), May 16, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 4)
      - Pittsburgh Subway "T" with Carol Brown, Pittsburgh, PA (2), May 20, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 5)
      - Ethel Allen School Chorus (1), June, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 6)
      - National Wheelchair Games, Edinboro University (5), June 13, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 7)
      - The Ginny Thornburgh Foundation (3), 1984-1985 (Box 1523, Folder 8)
      - Hand Rehabilitation Center (10), Summer, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 9)
      - Reservoir to River Run (1), September, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 10)
      - Penn National Horse Show (1), Fall, 1985 (Box 1523, Folder 11)